medicinalsupplementsummit.com 2018-08-23

# Privacy Policy - Medicinal Supplements Summit

Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information  
Last Updated May 2, 2018.

Thank you for visiting The Medicinal Supplements Summit. This notice explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. We reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy or any of our tools or services at any time and any changes will be effective upon being posted unless we advise otherwise. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you. We encourage you to periodically review this website for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, we ask that you do not use healthmeans.com, healthtalksonline.com, healthaffiliate.center or medicinalsupplementsummit.com.

## The Information We Collect.

By visiting healthmeans.com, healthtalksonline.com, healthaffiliate.center or medicinalsupplementsummit.com, you consent to the collection of the following information:

  * First Name and Email Address
  * Furthermore, you consent to the collection of certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e. generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac), your geolocation and the domain name of your Internet service provider. The event host(s) are the owners of the information collected on this site. If you do not want your personal information used by the host(s), HealthMeans or Health Talks Online as provided in this Privacy Policy, you should not access healthmeans.com, healthtalksonline.com, healthaffiliate.center or medicinalsupplementsummit.com.

## How We Use and Disclose the Information.

We will use the personal information you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted . Your First Name and Email Address will be used to send you the summit related content that you request. In addition, we may send you e-mails offering products or services which we think you may be interested in. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please click the unsubscribe link on the bottom of any of our communications. PLEASE NOTE: By opting out you WILL CONTINUE to receive limited notifications from us including purchase confirmations, password reset notifications, or any other account related correspondence.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe it is necessary or desirable to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, and/or to protect our rights and property. Regardless of the information collected, Health Talks Online and HealthMeans will not retain such information longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations.

## How We Share Your Personal Information.

The host of medicinalsupplementsummit.com retains explicit rights to this information and will NOT share the personal information you provide except with your explicit permission. You may withdraw your consent at anytime by using the “contact us” function on medicinalsupplementsummit.com/contact-us or the “manage subscription” link located at the bottom of all of our emails.

Our business needs may change from time to time and we reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without notifying the affected customers.

Our operations and maintenance contractors sometimes have limited access to your personally identifiable information while providing products or services to healthmeans.com, healthtalksonline.com, healthaffiliate.center or medicinalsupplementsummit.com. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us with credit card processing, e-mail distribution technology, services, and/or content for the operation and maintenance of our Web site. Access to your personally identifiable information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary for the contractor to perform its limited function. We also contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors 1) protect the privacy of your personally identifiable information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and 2) not use or disclose your personally identifiable information for any purpose other than providing us with products and services as required by law.

Health Means is committed to handling your customer information with high standards of information security. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.

## Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. We may also share aggregate information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies. If you do not consent to the use and disclosure of your anonymous information, please do not access healthmeans.com, healthtalksonline.com, healthaffiliate.center or medicinalsupplementsummit.com.

## Collection of Information by Others.

Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Cookies.

To enhance your online experience with us, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files placed on your hard disk by our web server to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to provide the personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our site is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). You can opt to have your browser reject cookies without any effect on your use of our site. If you do that, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our site to participate in certain promotions. You should also know that companies that advertise on our web site (and their agents) might use their own cookies. This policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies.

## Web Beacons.

Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons, which are also called single-pixel gifs. These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information, but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our website usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. Some of our Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.

## Discussions, Community Tools and Testimonials.

You agree that any information you submit to us through medicinalsupplementsummit.com may be used for promotional purposes. Because of the public nature of some of our services, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. We may also use a limited amount of information, such as first name, last initial and your town and state in marketing materials on the website. Your registration constitutes consent to this use.

## International Users.

If you are visiting medicinalsupplementsummit.com from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using any of our sites you authorize and specifically consent to the transfer of your personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us.

## How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information.

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you online, or how to correct any errors in such information, please contact us at healthmeans.com/contact-us. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
